wealthgardenblog.com 2015-03-24

# Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY FOR: wealthgardenblog

This privacy statement is created in order to demonstrate our continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with this web site.This privacy policy sets out how "wealthgardenblog" uses and protects any information that you give "wealthgardenblog" when you use this website.

"wealthgardenblog" is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and holds your privacy to the highest regard. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

"wealthgardenblog" may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from December 20, 2009.

We recognise the importance of protecting your privacy and our policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site.

What Information We Collect?

When you visit this web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide

Registration Information

When you register for any of our products, services or newsletters you will provide us information about yourself.

Credit Card Information

If you choose to avail of our services, you may need to give personal information and authorization to obtain information from various credit services. For example, you may need to provide the following information:

-Name

-Mailing address

-Email address

-Credit card number

-Name on credit card

-Credit card billing address

-Business and home phone number

Email Information

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

2\. Web Site Use Information

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and web server log files to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site.

How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing the products and services you requested, to process your payment, , to monitor the use of the service, our marketing and promotional efforts and improve our content and service offerings, and customize our site's content, layout, services and for other lawful purposes. These uses improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs.

Furthermore, such information may be shared with others on an aggregate basis. Personally identifiable information or business information will not be shared with parties except as required by law.

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Website, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at the link provided on the newsletter.

What Are Cookies?

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Browsers are usually set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you may alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function as effectively when viewed by the users. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses.

How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?

As you visit and browse our Web site, the site uses cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from having to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our clients. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not intentionally store any personal information that your browser provided to us in your cookies.

IP Addresses

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as traffic data so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

Sharing and Selling Information

We do not share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that uniquely identify a subscriber (such as email addresses or personal details) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide services that you have requested.

How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?

You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing us at the usual address.

What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. We may also disclose account information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or to protect the safety of our users and the Public.

What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites, which have a link on our Website, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

Your Consent

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice.

Choice/Opt-In/Opt-Out

This site allows visitors to unsubscribe so that they will not receive future messages. After unsubscribing we will discontinue sending the particular messages as soon as technically feasible.

Surveys &amp; Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

Persons under 18

Children are not eligible to use our services unsupervised and we ask that children (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians.

Acquisition or Changes in Ownership

In the event that the web site (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred.

Policy Revisions

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this privacy policy, we will email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

QUESTIONS

You may direct enquiries to:  [admin@wealthgardenblog.com](mailto:admin@wealthgardenblog.com)

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-creation/334-wealth-creation-courses-guerrilla-business-school)If youre going to work hard anyway, you might as well get rich and the quicker the better. At Guerrilla Business School, a panel of expert millionaire business owners share their secrets of success so you can quit wasting your time with strIf youre going to work hard anyway, you might as well get rich...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1271-wealth-management-basics-dynamic-wealth-management), Estimate the potential cost of waiting to purchase a long-term care insurance policy. Women and Retirement Investing Some ctors that may affect P/E ratios and what they might reveal about individual stocks and broader market trends. How m, Estimate the potential cost of waiting to purchase a long-term...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1415-wealth-management-funds-sovereign-wealth-funds-news)The International Working Group of Sovereign Wealth Funds (IWG) announced today in Kuwait City the establishment of the International Forum of Sovereign Wealth Funds (Forum). The Kuwait Declaration, issued at the end of a two-day meeting hoThe International Working Group of Sovereign Wealth Funds (IWG)...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-creation/325-what-is-wealth-consciousness?-wealth-creation-courses)Contact No: +91 80-28022100, 9742203311; Fax: +91 80 28022123; Email: Whats stopping us from expressing our ability to create wealth? Here we look at some common myths and mindsets we carry about wealth and how to break free of them: Keep y Contact No: +91 80-28022100, 9742203311; Fax: +91 80 28022123;...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-creation/105-wealth-creation-australia-australia)Contact us Financial planning advice for you and your mily including superannuation, rollovers, savings plans, life insurance and tax-effective investments Useful resources: Learn more... Learn more... I need to: Quick forms: Individual TaxContact usFinancial planning advice for you and your mily...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/distribution-of-wealth/672-graphic-view-of-wealth-distribution-in-america)March 19, 2013 at 12:25 pmThe distribution of wealth? Why do we not recognize those who have worked hard to get to where they are? If the case is that they have stepped on others to get to where they are (and we know that this is not the caMarch 19, 2013 at 12:25 pmThe distribution of wealth? Why do we...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/definition-of-wealth/567-economic-definition-of-wealth-what-is-the-definition-of-econ)Economic equality refers to an economy in that all of the inhabitants are equally wealthy, and have the same status in the economy, because they have had the same opportunities, non discriminant on race, gender, skill, culture, or wealth coEconomic equality refers to an economy in that all of the...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-strategies/833-independence-wealth-strategies)Newark, DE 19713 10 Lake Center Executive Park Map and Directions 800.682.8128 Suite 100 We have representatives in this office licensed and registered to offer products and services in [PA, NJ, DE, NY]. Licenses and registrations will varyNewark, DE 1971310 Lake Center Executive ParkMap and...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/economic-wealth/1872-ft-wealth-wealth-economic-times)Art forgeries, Ukraines oligarchs, and YouTube millionaires: this issue covers wealth around the world Regenerative medicines that were once the domain of science fiction and alchemy are moving into the mainstream Billionaire Petter StordalArt forgeries, Ukraines oligarchs, and YouTube millionaires:...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1023-why-choose-rbc-wealth-management??-wealth-managers)RBC Wealth Management offers integrated wealth management solutions to meet the sophisticated financial needs of wealthy individuals, as well as corporate and institutional clients. We offer investment management, trust and estate planning,RBC Wealth Management offers integrated wealth management...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1011-2plan-wealth-management)Registered in England Number: 05998270 Chris joined the financial services industry over 20 years ago as a financial adviser. Following rapid career growth, he became the Executive National Sales Director for Positive Solutions, which he jo Registered in England Number: 05998270Chris joined the...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1368-wealth-ma?-wealth-management-software)At this event, attendees To help you come alive. Its true that WEALTH Magazine is packed with financial intelligence to help you capture the goldand escape the grenadesin todays globally interconnected economy. But we have a more profound mAt this event, attendees To help you come alive. Its true that...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/distribution-of-wealth/806-global-wealth-distribution-richest-1-percent-hold-46-percent)The biggest emerging markets, the so-called BRIC countries - Brazil, Russia, India, and China - are each estimated to have around 5,830 such ultra-high net worth individuals. Credit Suisse said there were 98,700 individuals with net worth eThe biggest emerging markets, the so-called BRIC countries -...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-creation/109-wealth-creation-plans-wealth-creation-and-mortgage-planning)First we must explain the difference between return of investment and return on investment. Return OF investment is simply getting back the money that you put in. Return ON investment is difference between the end value of your investment aFirst we must explain the difference between return of...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1286-wealth-management-presentation-patterson-wealth-management)A will may be only one of the documents you needand one ctor to considerwhen it comes to managing your estate. We believe in strong individual relationships that stand the test of time. Jeff Patterson, Managing Partner of Patterson Wealth MA will may be only one of the documents you needand one ctor to...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-creation/202-wealth-creation-australia-wealth-creation-in-w)(08) 93012200McKinley Plowman Naylor for all their business or personal accounting needs. Specialising in tax and property accounting, arrange an appointment with us today. Find out more Harts Financial Solutions is a privately owned financ(08) 93012200McKinley Plowman & Associates  is a leading Western...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/secrets-of-wealth/1666-secrets-of-wealth-free-ebooks)Formats for Kindle, NOOK, iPad, Kobo and all mobile devices. Simply set up your own Personal Account Priority Access to support and our latest arrivals. Any Format for eReaders, Tablets Android Mobile Apps! UNlimited Downloads! Read ALL the Formats for Kindle, NOOK, iPad, Kobo and all mobile...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/secrets-of-wealth/1617-secret-of-wealth-the-\(hidden\)-secret-of-wealth)For example, whether you choose to spend an extra hour watching YouTube videos or checking in with friends on Facebook instead of educating yourself on the different vehicles (such as Ambit) that can help you become independently wealthy, pFor example, whether you choose to spend an extra hour watching...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/distribution-of-wealth/710-global-wealth-distribution-global-wealth-advisory)NJ Global Invest (Ltd.) is a new venture wherein NJ seeks to offer a Global Wealth Advisory platform to advisors for offshore funds across the globe. Website: The vision at Global Wealth Advisory platform is to offer a single window for invNJ Global Invest (Ltd.) is a new venture wherein NJ seeks to...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1220-donnelly-wealth-management-chiefexecutivenet)Chief Executives groundbreaking research on executive compensation describes in detail executive compensation packages. The report specifically covers CEO salaries, including the average ceo salary for private companies. But CEO salary andChief Executives groundbreaking research on executive...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/economic-wealth/1969-the-economic-times-average-billionaire-has-4-homes;-loves-ya)The average billionaire is worth $ 3 billion with a liquidity of 18 per cent, equal to $ 545 million in cash and other liquid assets per person, suggesting that the old mantra of cash is king remains as relevant as ever. When it comes to ed The average billionaire is worth $ 3 billion with a...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/means-wealth/1777-1000-names-of-lord-vishnu-\(sahasra-nama\)-with-meaning-meanin)jnaanagamyah = one who is experienced through pure knowledge vyaaptah = the pervader vrishakarmaa = he whose every act is righteous If the copyright author of any wall want his/her wall removed or to be credited then contact us!. Privacy Po jnaanagamyah = one who is experienced through pure knowledge...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/economic-wealth/1874-economic-wealth-cjm-wealth-management)Melville, NY, February, 3, 2014 Conquest Press has named Charles Joseph Massimo to their 2014 Americas Select Financial Advisors Book. The nations top financial advisors were invited to apply for acceptance in this book. These Financial AdvMelville, NY, February, 3, 2014 Conquest Press has named Charles...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-creation/319-congress-teaching-it)The Congressional Timeline, developed and maintained by The Dirksen Congressional Center, arrays more than 900 of the nations laws on a timeline beginning with the first Congress in 1789 and continuing to the present. A second timeline bandThe Congressional Timeline, developed and maintained by The...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/secrets-of-wealth/1688-secrets-of-wealth-home-wealth-secrets)What I do have is something that I know for sure that even the most average guy can use to make money right out of the starting gate. Its scary how the economy seems to be spiraling out of control. Maybe take a nice slow soak in the tub befWhat I do have is something that I know for sure that even the...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/economic-wealth/1924-define-economic-wealth-economic-income-vs-gross-income)The primary difference between gross income and economic income is that gross income results from business transactions and economic income results from economic events. Gross income is realized, meaning that a transaction took place and reThe primary difference between gross income and economic income...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/economic-wealth/1945-ancient-egyptian-the-wealth-economic-times)The vast majority of the population, probably more than nine tenths during the first two millennia of Egypts history, lived on the land Juan Carlos Moreno Garca, 2008, Estates (Old Kingdom), in Elizabeth Frood and Willeke Wendrich (eds.) UCThe vast majority of the population, probably more than nine...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1375-personal-financial-services-family-wealth-management)The extensive, multi-year plan would gradually diversify his investments and distribute assets among his children. Working together, his advisors set up several different entities, including LLCs, LLPs, and at least a dozen different trustsThe extensive, multi-year plan would gradually diversify his...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/means-wealth/1863-deepak-chopra-what-is-meaning-of-wealth)At one time or another, the misery of lower back pain is felt by everyone, which is no surprise. Our upright spine is as unique to being human as having an opposable thumb. But where anyone can see that using our hands involves every aspectAt one time or another, the misery of lower back pain is felt by...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-creation/75-wealth-creation-ideas-ignitepoint)Imagine a TEDx-style event where you can mention God, Jesus Christ and tell your ith-promoting stories! Learn more here. Im going to share something radical with you, something that flies in the ce of what most of us believe about God, ours Imagine a TEDx-style event where you can mention God, Jesus...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-creation/299-agnew-wealth-creations?-wealth-creations)x: (02) 4423 7344 Nowra NSW 2541 P.O.Box 1616 Suite 1/37 Dalton Drive 55 Bridge Road Maroochydore QLD 4558 (by appointment only) ph: 1300 237 333 Agnew Wealth Creations see map Agnew Wealth Creations is passionate for your prosperity. We un x: (02) 4423 7344 Nowra NSW 2541 P.O.Box 1616 Suite 1/37...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-creation/248-wealth-creation-australia-rfs-finance)Now more than ever, Australians need good financial advice. Good financial advice helps you make the most of what you have while helping you to create a comfortable future for you and your mily. RFS Finance is not tied to a limited range of Now more than ever, Australians need good financial advice....

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/definition-of-wealth/510-waste-to-wealth)Access to the Internet is an essential infrastructure for any community that cares about economic development, quality of life, and educational opportunities. Unfortunately, most communities are presently dependent on a few unaccountable abAccess to the Internet is an essential infrastructure for any...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/definition-of-wealth/394-economic-value-added)Economic, Clinical and Humanistic Outcomes Economic Trends and Issues Shareholder Value Added Economic Threshold Level economic theory This measure was devised by Stern Stewart & Co. and is used as a way to ascertain the true economic profiEconomic, Clinical and Humanistic OutcomesEconomic Trends and...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/definition-of-wealth/390-talkwealth-management-wealth-management-definition)Wealth Management advisors typically limit their services to clients that have more than $5 million in investable funds. Some banks require an even higher amount of funds in order to focus attention and limited resources on investing clientWealth Management advisors typically limit their services to...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-strategies/812-microsoft-confirms-bates-reller-to-exit-company)Tony Bates has decided this is the right time for him to look for his next opportunity. Tony came to the company via the Skype acquisition, where he was CEO of Skype, and did a great job of successfully landing that team and continuing to b Tony Bates has decided this is the right time for him to look...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/definition-of-wealth/427-definition-of-wealth-michael-jacksons-recording-engineers-sc)The Bruce Swedien Recording Method is available in bookstores and on Amazon. Youre not going to find the right mic choice on Google, you have to figure it out for yourself, by listening to the sound, corrections, and listening again. SwedieThe Bruce Swedien Recording Method is available in bookstores...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1153-global-wealth-management-institutional-services)Corporate Services Tax Planning Investment Strategy Twentieth Century Because Atlantic Financial has no management ties to specific money managers or mutual fund companies, we are able to remain objective in our recommendations. For corporaCorporate Services Tax Planning Investment Strategy Twentieth...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-creation/363-wealth-creation-courses-wealth-creation-courses)This entry was posted on Tuesday, November 29th, 2011 at 1:13 pm and is filed under Making Money. Both comments and pings are currently closed. Unfortunately, I dont think there is a sure-fire magic formula to becoming rich. Youll probablyThis entry was posted on Tuesday, November 29th, 2011 at 1:13 pm...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/secrets-of-wealth/1611-secret-to-wealth-bob-proctor---the-secret-to-wealth-\(12)size=60 onclick=javascript:document.linkForm.video_play.focus();document.linkForm.video_play.select(); readonly=readonly /> (Put this video on your website. Works on Friendster, eBay, Blogger, MySpace!)size=60 onclick=javascript:document.linkForm.video_play.focus();document.linkForm.video_play.select();...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1479-our-wealth-management-approach?-wealth-management-canada)Step 1: Introduction RBC Wealth Management Canada RBC Dominion Securities A Personalized Approach Our Wealth Management Approach Because these various aspects of managing wealth are all interconnected, we will create a total, coordinated weStep 1: IntroductionRBC Wealth Management Canada RBC Dominion...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-creation/271-wealth-creation-courses-create-courses-new-definition-of-tec)Quiz always had a special place for them in the dictionary of youth and remained so popular as well. It is not only the question of popularity, but to cushion its roots as well. This modus operandi is so effective that it can attract the in Quiz always had a special place for them in the dictionary of...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1025-rates-vary-widely-as-more-advisers-use-fees)Still, Trott thinks the spread is so large it shows that advisers are too often using hearsay to set their rates. He concedes that his firm would benefit from more people seeking scientific-based calculations, but says advisers should lookStill, Trott thinks the spread is so large it shows that advisers...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1090-online-s-wealth-management-courses)High-quality small business management courses taught by business department culty with a wealth of real-world management expertise Small business represents the lifeblood of the American economy and a significant generator of employment. AHigh-quality small business management courses taught by...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1495-wealth-management-education-byrne-wealth-management-llc)Byrne Wealth Management LLC, Omaha,NE Byrne Wealth Management LLC is a full service investment advisory firm providing portfolio management and financial planning services located in Omaha, NE.Byrne Wealth Management LLC, Omaha,NE Byrne Wealth Management LLC is a full service investment advisory firm...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/economic-wealth/1889-politicalnews?-wealth-economic-times)I would agree with much of what is said here, but what is the solution? If you argue that democracy is fundamental to good governance, why are we arguing against Scotland taking its own destiny in hand, and at the same time the case that thI would agree with much of what is said here, but what is the...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1238-wealth-management-presentation-types-of-risk)b. Intangible hazard: - attitudes and culture more of less physical in nature 1. M oral hazard: - Fraud increase in the possibility or putting fire to a ctory running in losses. 2. Morale Hazard: - indifference the attitude of indifferenceb. Intangible hazard: - attitudes and culture more of less...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/economic-wealth/1884-economic-times-wealth-financial-times-lexicon)air passenger dutyAir Passenger Duty (APD) is a per passenger charge on air travel from UK airports (other than the Scottish Highlands and Islands and long... An income statement is a report showing how much a company earned over a given peair passenger dutyAir Passenger Duty (APD) is a per passenger...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/wealth-management/1123-wealth-management-chicago-chicago-wealth-management)Jim and Martha, an elderly couple with a sizable estate, were referred to us for estate planning advice. ... Read More We are a private, independent investment and wealth management firm serving high net worth individuals and milies. OurJim and Martha, an elderly couple with a sizable estate, were...

[](http://wealthgardenblog.com/index.php/definition-of-wealth/593-what-is-the-definition-of-wealth-jealous)feeling resentment against someone because of that persons rivalry, success, or advantages (often followed by ): wear black stockings, also be jealous. Dan. skinsyg jealous, lit. skin-sick, is from skind hide, skin said to be explained by Sfeeling resentment against someone because of that persons...
